<?xml version="1.0"?><MetadataTemplate><Dataset><Code>D1</Code><Title>A short name given to a dataset (e.g., Gull GPS movement data)</Title><Acronym>What is the acronym of the dataset (e.g., GULLGPS)?</Acronym><Path>Path of the dataset in the data archive.</Path><Description>GPS movement data of 5 GPS monitored seagulls in Amsterdam, The Netherlands, monitored over a period of 3 years (March 2016-March 2019). GPS movement data has been collected using uva-bits tags and were subsequently stored in the uva-bits bird tracking database.</Description><Creator>An entity primarily responsible for making the resource.</Creator><Publisher>An entity responsible for making the resource available.</Publisher><Contributor>An entity responsible for making contributions to the resource.</Contributor><Type>Collection</Type><Format>The file format of the resource (e.g., csv, tiff, rds, shapefile, fasta).</Format><OS>If the dataset is only readable for a specific Operating System, please specify that Operating System.</OS><Software>If the dataset is only readable by a specific software, please specify that software.</Software><Identifier>The unique identifier of the resource (e.g., doi).</Identifier><Source>A related resource from which the described resource is derived. For example, a dataset might be an extraction from an existing database, a digitalized museum collection,... Please make sure that the resource can be easily derived, for example by including a weblink.</Source><Rights>Information about the rights held in and over the resource (e.g., University of Amsterdam)</Rights><Language>A language of a resource.</Language><SpatialCoverage>The spatial location or area of the resource. This can be specified by the coordinates of a bounding box,the centroid of an area, the coordinates of a location, but also by the name of the place (e.g. a specific valley, village, city, country, continent).</SpatialCoverage><ProjectionSystem>In case of spatial data, that includes coordinates, please provide the projection system of the resource (e.g., WGS84 EPSG:4326).</ProjectionSystem><TemporalCoverage>The timestamp (YYYY-MM-DD hh:mm:ss) or time period (from YYYY-MM-DD to YYYY-MM-DD) of the resource. Please use the format YYYY-MM-DD for the date and hh:mm:ss the time.</TemporalCoverage><Keywords>bla</Keywords><SizeMB>1</SizeMB><Variable><Name>Name of a variable/column of a dataset.</Name><Unit>Unit of the variable/column (e.g., meter, square meter, degrees).</Unit><Datatype>Datatype of the variable/column (e.g., double precision, integer, timestamp).</Datatype><Description>A clear description of the column/variable.</Description></Variable><Variable><Name>Name of a variable/column of a dataset.</Name><Unit>Unit of the variable/column (e.g., meter, square meter, degrees).</Unit><Datatype>Datatype of the variable/column (e.g., double precision, integer, timestamp).</Datatype><Description>A clear description of the column/variable.</Description></Variable></Dataset></MetadataTemplate>